EdwardsBJeremy@gmail.com 504-284-8616

2633 Iberville St., Apt. A New Orleans, LA 70119

## Summary

Accomplished Desktop Support Technician with knowledge of remote hardware and software support across multiple operating systems and devices. Experienced working within Desktop teams and multiple ticketing systems supporting thousands of end-users in remote locations across the country. Excellent communicator with bilingual skills.

#### **Experience**

Desktop Support Technician, Boasso America (Chalmette, LA; Nov 2016 - Feb 2018)

- Worked with both Windows and Chrome based devices
- Troubleshooted printers, network issues, computers, in-house software, etc.
- Managed IT assets and users using Google Admin and AD
- Set up a print server with over 150 networked printers
- Supported over 1000 users located at more than 10 locations around the U.S.
- Used ChangeGear to document and track tickets
- Imaged/set up new Windows & Chrome devices for deployment
- Tracked IT assets
- Managed distribution lists
- Managed employee roles and access rights

Desktop Support Technician, Whitney Bank (New Orleans, LA; Feb. 2014 - Nov. 2016)

- Troubleshooted printers, network issues, computers, in-house software, etc.
- Worked on a project to set up a print server with over 200 printers
- Supported over 4000 users located at various bank branches from Texas to Florida.
- Used ServiceNow to document and track tickets
- Imaged/set up new Windows & Chrome devices for deployment
- Tracked IT Assets

Front End Developer, Mandle-Edwards Surveying (Harahan, LA; 2012 - 2016)

- Designed and coded the company website using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Created an Access database for storing customer data and invoicing customers
- Upgraded aging computer and network infrastructure of the business.

# **Education, Awards, & Certs**

Diploma in French Language Studies (DELF), B2 Level, 2017 Recipient of UNO's James Whitlow Award for Outstanding Achievement, 2016 University of New Orleans, New Orleans, LA; French, B.A., 2013 - 2016

### Volunteering

Global Ambassador of French, Duolingo (New Orleans, LA; 2017 - 2018) Organizer, Peace Advocacy Network (New Orleans, LA; 2017, 2018)

CSS, HTML, OS X, Windows, Linux, Photoshop, Photography, Python, Javascript, Networking, Active Directory, Hardware, iPhone, Android, Print Servers, Microsoft Office, Printer Support, Technical Support, Public Speaking, Google Admin, Adobe Dreamweaver, InDesign, Xcode, VIM, Ubuntu, Bomgar, Zoho Assist, Ultra VNC, Chrome RDP, TeamViewer, ChangeGear, Chrome Remote Desktop, ServiceNow, User Administration, VPN, Citrix, ActiveSync, Javascript, ¡Query, Bootstrap,

#### Lanquages English: **Native**

French: Advanced, C1 Japanese: Beginner,, A1 Mandarin: Intermediate, B1 Spanish: Intermediate, B1